A green build is not a shippable game. PlayReceipt is an evidence gate for AI-built games.
It returns Pass, Repair, Human Review, or Unverified—never one flattering synthetic score.
The real snapshot completed 2,000 seeded runs with zero crashes and zero stalls.
But weak strategy, missing reduced motion, and no human calibration keep it at Repair.
Now the judge can paste a new JSON evidence bundle with no account and issue a receipt.
The result is exact, copyable, downloadable, and capped at a Human Review boundary.
The trail shows Ingest, Judge, Repair Plan, and where automation must stop.
The browser, API, CLI, and GitHub Action all call the same deterministic audit engine.
Repair and Unverified fail CI. Human Review stays successful with a visible warning.
Eleven regression tests cover adapter parity and abuse boundaries with zero runtime dependencies.
Codex and GPT-5.6 shaped the product contract, implementation, tests, and browser verification.
Try your own evidence, then inspect every claim in the public repository.